signaturevacations.com 2005-04-04

# Our Privacy Policy - SIGNATURE Vacations

Privacy Policy  

SIGNATURE VACATIONS, a division of First Choice Canada Inc. is committed to protecting the privacy of your personal information. We have developed this policy and related procedures to comply with the Personal Information Protection and Electronic Documents Act.

SIGNATURE VACATIONS is responsible for personal information it holds or has under its control, including personal information it passes on to others with your permission. We have designated a Privacy Officer to ensure our compliance with legislation and this policy. Our Privacy officer will receive and respond to your inquiries and complaints regarding the protection and privacy of your personal information, and deal with requests for access to your information.

**What categories of personal information will SIGNATURE VACATIONS collect and hold?**

When you browse this site, we do not collect personal information about you. The only way we can collect any kind of personal information is if you give it to us.

The nature of personal information we collect may include:

  * Information we receive from you when you book travel either through our Web site, over the telephone, in writing or in person.. This information may include such details as your name, your address and your credit card details; 
  * Information we receive from you on a volunteer basis if we conduct a survey of your preferences, needs and interests;
  * Information about your transactions with us, our affiliates, or third parties such as air carriers or hotels.  

**What does SIGNATURE VACATIONS do with the information collected?**

SIGNATURE VACATIONS may use the information provided by you for one or more of the following purposes:

  * to contact you about your holiday;
  * to contact you with details of other products and services that are offered by SIGNATURE VACATIONS, or that are available to SIGNATURE VACATIONS customers from its selected trading partners;
  * to respond to your inquiries about your travel and other services;
  * to meet legal, security and regulatory requirements;
  * to understand your needs and preferences and to offer products and services to meet those needs.

**Will SIGNATURE ever disclose my information to its affiliates?**

SIGNATURE VACATIONS and our affiliates may share with each other marketing lists (lists of customers that meet certain general non-sensitive criteria). This information may include your name, address, gender, preferred language of communication, preferences, needs, interests and information about trips you have booked with SIGNATURE VACATIONS and its affiliates in the past. The sharing of such information is to assist our affiliates to offer products and services that are most likely to be of interest to you.

**Will SIGNATURE VACATIONS ever disclose my information to third parties?**

We disclose your information to third parties for the purpose of completing your transaction with us, providing services to you and for the purposes of associated administration and obtaining professional advice.

Third parties to whom we will disclose your information may include air carriers, hotel operators, and other travel service providers whom we have retained to provide services to you. We may also provide your information to a third party credit card processing company that will use your information in settling your account with your bank or card issuer.

Additionally, SIGNATURE VACATIONS may also send your information to its selected trading partners and other third parties so that they may contact you to let you know of both travel and non-travel-related products and services.

If you purchase a cancellation or travel insurance policy to cover any aspect of a SIGNATURE VACATIONS' product, and you subsequently make a claim to the insurer under that policy, SIGNATURE VACATIONS may provide information to the insurer, if requested, with respect to cancellation charges applicable to the particular product, or the date the trip was cancelled by you, or the date any other relevant event giving rise to coverage under the policy occurred.

**What other information is collected?**

When you view our Web site by linking from another Web page we may store the name of that Web page for purposes of internal administration. Also please note that any contact with SIGNATURE VACATIONS, either online or by telephone, may be recorded for training and monitoring purposes.

**Where is my personal information stored?**

All personal information is stored in secure databases at secure addresses to prevent unauthorized access.

**What is a 'cookie'?**

Cookies are small files that are sent to your browser (for example Internet Explorer or Netscape) and stored on your computer's hard disk. They only identify your computer and not you personally. 

**How does SIGNATURE VACATIONS use cookies?**

Cookies help speed up the booking process so that you do not need to re-type the same information again and again. We use cookies to measure site usage such as entry and exit points of visitors, how many people visit a certain section or page and details of searches performed and related information. If you are making a purchase we will also use cookies to keep track of the transaction from one page to the next. If you choose to, we will store your email address and password in the cookie, in a secure form, to allow you to login automatically. Other than this, we do not store any other information in the cookie, or use it for any other purpose.

**What if I sign-up as a My Signature member or subscribe to a newsletter?**

When you sign up as a My Signature member or newsletter subscriber, you will receive occasional communication by email such as a Welcome message, Newsletter Subscribe or Unsubscribe Confirmation, E-newsletters, Password Reminder if requested, Trip Reminders, or a reminder if you account is inactive for a period of time. These emails may contain your name, your user name, your password or your travel itinerary if you booked through this Web site.  

**How will I know if my online booking is confirmed?** Each time you purchase travel through signaturevacations.com you will receive confirmation of your travel itinerary by e-mail. In the event that your travel plans are disrupted because of mechanical, weather, or carrier business conditions, SIGNATURE VACATIONS may contact you to inform you of these disruptions and help you make alternative arrangements.

**Where are the credit/debit card numbers stored?**

Your credit/debit card number is not stored on any file within the SIGNATURE VACATIONS Web site and is only used to complete the transaction. The credit/debit number is passed through to our credit/debit card company for validation and debit via our booking system. Once you enter your credit/debit number it is encrypted so that nobody else can read it, and is not printed out or displayed on any other computer.

**How will I know if you change this privacy policy?**

Any changes to the Privacy Policy will be made to this page. Your continued use of this site will constitute your agreement to the changed Terms and Conditions of using this site.

**What about the other Web sites you link to?**

SIGNATURE VACATIONS, its employees, contractors, agents, and owners are not responsible for the privacy policies or content of any Web site which it may link to. 

**Consent**

By disclosing your personal information to us using this Web site, over the telephone, in writing or in person with a customer service representative of SIGNATURE VACATIONS or one of our affiliates or through a travel agent, you consent to the collection, storage and processing of your personal information by SIGNATURE VACATIONS as stated in this Privacy Policy.  

**How can I access the personal information SIGNATURE VACATIONS has about me?**

We will establish and maintain a file of personal information about each SIGNATURE VACATIONS customer. Your file will be kept by us and will be accessible to you. Only SIGNATURE VACATIONS employees, agencies and advisors who need access to your file in the course of their duties and for the purposes identified will be given access to it.

You have the right to access your file and to request rectification of any personal information in it that may be obsolete, incomplete or incorrect. 

You can request the Customer Access to Personal Information Request Form by writing to the Privacy Officer at our offices in Toronto.

We will take steps to validate the identity of the person making the request to ensure we do not provide information to anyone not authorized to receive it. We may use your personal information to do so. We may charge you a reasonable administration fee for providing access to your file in accordance with your request. Normally we will respond to your request within 30 days of receiving it.

**Contact Information**

Privacy Officer  
SIGNATURE VACATIONS  
160 Bloor Street East, Suite 400  
Toronto, Ontario, Canada  
M4W 1B9

**Handling of Complaints**

SIGNATURE VACATIONS believes communication is beneficial to both our customers and ourselves, whether it is to answer a question, solve a problem or share a success story.

We welcome positive comments from customers, however it is equally important for us to know when you have a problem so we can resolve it and retain your confidence. At the same time, we use your feedback to continuously improve the quality of the products and services we offer. 

There are a variety of ways for you to provide positive feedback or express your concerns about your experiences with SIGNATURE VACATIONS. We encourage customers to provide their feedback online at <http://www.signaturevacations.com/CRfeedback.html>
